Jane Harman Papers, 1960-1998 (ongoing) (bulk 1993-1998)
Sophia Smith Collection, Smith College
- SERIES IV. LEGISLATIVE FILES 1993-98
  - Legislative staff files
    - Danny Geffen and Maria Alongi
      - Letters, 1994-98
        - Tobacco Tax - children's health (Box 79, Folder 10)
        - Tucker, Regina (Box 79, Folder 11)
        - UCLA - Neighborhood Knowledge Los Angeles (NKLA) program (Box 79, Folder 12)
        - Veteran status of women - Women's Health Initiative (Box 79, Folder 13)
        - Violence Against Women Act (VAWA) conferees (Box 79, Folder 14)
        - Violence Against Women Act (VAWA) priorities (Box 79, Folder 15)
        - Women's issues funding - Labor/HHS FY 95 (Box 79, Folder 16)
        - Women's Rights Beijing - Albright (Box 79, Folder 17)
        - World Trade Organization (WTO) - Clinton (Box 79, Folder 18)
        - Zana, Leyla (Box 79, Folder 19)
      - Social Security Reform, 105th, 1997-98
        - Briefing for California Congressional staff (Box 79, Folder 20)
        - General (Box 79, Folder 21)
      - Trade, 103rd-105th, 1993-98
        - California companies - Guanzhou Airport (Box 79, Folder 22)
        - Cuban Humanitarian Trade Act (Box 79, Folder 23)
        - Fast Track Trade Authority (Box 79, Folder 24-26)
        - General System of Preferences (GSP) program (Box 79, Folder 27)
        - Hughes satellite (Box 80, Folder 1)
        - International Monetary Fund funding (Box 80, Folder 2)
        - Jackson-Vanik Vietnam (Box 80, Folder 3)
        - Most-Favored-Nation - China (Box 80)
          - 1993-96 (Box 80, Folder 4-7)
          - 1996-99 (Box 81, Folder 1-3)
        - North American Free Trade Agreement (NAFTA) (Box 81, Folder 4)
      - Welfare reform, 105th, 1997-98
        - California reform (Box 81, Folder 5)
        - California waiver (Box 81, Folder 6)
        - General (Box 82, Folder 1-3)
        - Welfare and Medicaid Reform Act of 1996 (Box 82, Folder 4)
      - Women and families, 1994-98
        - American Association of University Women voting record (Box 83, Folder 1)
        - Adoption (Box 83, Folder 2)
        - Beijing (Box 83, Folder 3-7)
        - Child care (Box 83, Folder 8)
        - Child Protection Act (Box 83, Folder 9)
        - Children's Gun Violence Protection Act (Box 83, Folder 10)
        - Congressional Caucus for Women's Issues, 20th anniversary (Box 83, Folder 11)
        - Convention on the Elimination of All Forms of Discrimination Against Women (CEDAW) (Box 83, Folder 12)
        - Domestic violence (Box 83, Folder 13)
        - HR 3855 - Children's Hospital (Box 84, Folder 1)
        - Klugman, Kate (Box 84, Folder 2)
        - Little Rock Nine (Box 84, Folder 3)
        - Suicide prevention (Box 84, Folder 4)
        - Suffrage statues - Harman remarks (Box 84, Folder 5)
        - Violence Against Women Act of 1994 (VAWA) (Box 84, Folder 6)
        - Violence Against Women Act of 1998 (Box 84, Folder 7)
        - Women in the Military Service for America (WIMSA) - Women Veterans Memorial (Box 84, Folder 8)
        - Women, Infants and Children (WIC) nutrition program (Box 84, Folder 9)
        - Women's Caucus-105th Congress (Box 84, Folder 10)
        - Women's opportunities - Harman (Box 84, Folder 11)
    - Ron Stone
      - Energy and environment, 1993-97 (Box 84)
        - Airline ticket tax (Box 85, Folder 1)
        - Alameda Corridor (Box 85, Folder 2)
        - Ballona Wetlands (Box 85, Folder 3)
        - Bay-Delta Estuary (Box 85, Folder 4)
        - California Desert Protection Act (Box 85, Folder 5)
        - CALSTART (Box 85, Folder 6)
        - Campaign finance (Box 85, Folder 7)
        - Catalina (Box 85, Folder 8)
        - Chevron (Box 85, Folder 9)
        - Clean air (Box 85, Folder 10)
        - Clean Water Act (Box 85, Folder 11)
        - DDT/420 (Box 85, Folder 12)
        - Del Amo event, 3 Mar 1997 (Box 85, Folder 13)
        - Douglas Street (Box 85, Folder 14)
        - Electrical Transportation Test Center (Box 85, Folder 15)
        - Endangered Species Act (Box 85, Folder 16)
        - Environmental op-ed (Box 86, Folder 1)
        - Environmental paper (Box 86, Folder 2)
        - Environmental politics (Box 86, Folder 3)
        - Environmental roundtables (Box 86, Folder 4)
        - Flow control (Box 86, Folder 5)
        - Forests (Box 86, Folder 6)
        - Grazing fees (Box 86, Folder 7)
        - Green Framing Systems (Box 86, Folder 8)
        - Green Scissors (Box 86, Folder 9)
        - Ham radio/spectrums (Box 86, Folder 10)
        - Hear the Bay (Box 86, Folder 11)
        - High-speed ground transportation initiative/ Maglev (Box 86, Folder 12)
        - Highway safety (Box 86, Folder 13)
        - Hughes (Box 86, Folder 14)
        - Honda (Box 86, Folder 15)
        - Hyperion (Box 86, Folder 16)
        - Intelligent Vehicle Highway Systems (IVHS) (Box 86, Folder 17)
        - Interior appropriations, FY 96-97 (Box 86, Folder 18-19)
        - Japan air issue (Box 86, Folder 20)
        - LAX (Box 87, Folder 1-2)
        - LAX master plan (Box 87, Folder 3)
        - League of Conservation Voters (LCV) (Box 87, Folder 4)
        - Marina del Rey (Box 87, Folder 5)
        - Metropolitan Transportation Authority (MTA) (Box 87, Folder 6)
        - Mining law reform (Box 87, Folder 7)
        - National Biological Survey (Box 87, Folder 8)
        - National Information Infrastructure (NII) (Box 87, Folder 9)
        - National parks (Box 87, Folder 10)
        - National Weather Service (Box 87, Folder 11)
        - Natural disasters (Box 88, Folder 1)
        - Natural gas vehicle (NGV) (Box 88, Folder 2)
        - Neighborhood Electric Vehicles (NEV) (Box 88, Folder 3)
        - National Oceanic and Atmospheric Administration (Box 88, Folder 4)
        - Offshore oil drilling (Box 88, Folder 5)
        - Pesticides (Box 88, Folder 6)
        - Presidio (Box 88, Folder 7)
        - Project California (Box 88, Folder 8)
        - Radon (Box 88, Folder 9)
        - Rail electrification (Box 88, Folder 10)
        - Railroads (Box 88, Folder 11)
        - Recycling (Box 88, Folder 12)
        - Redondo Beach (Box 88, Folder 13)
        - Reformulated gas (Box 88, Folder 14)
        - Regulatory reform (Box 88, Folder 15)
        - Renewables (Box 88, Folder 16)
        - Safe drinking water (Box 88, Folder 17)
        - Santa Monica Airport (Box 88, Folder 18)
        - Santa Monica Bay Restoration Project (SMBRP) (Box 88, Folder 19)
        - Securities reform (Box 88, Folder 20)
        - Solar energy (Box 88, Folder 21)
        - Southern California Association of Governments (SCAG) (Box 89, Folder 1)
        - Superfund (Box 89, Folder 2)
        - Supertug (Box 89, Folder 3)
        - Takings (Box 89, Folder 4)
        - Telecommunications (Box 89, Folder 5)
        - Unfunded mandates reform (Box 89, Folder 6)
        - Ward Valley (Box 89, Folder 7)
        - West Basin recycling (Box 89, Folder 8)
        - Wetlands (Box 89, Folder 9)
        - Wind energy (Box 89, Folder 10)
        - Xcorp (Box 89, Folder 11)
        - Zero Emissions Surface Transit (ZEST) bus (Box 89, Folder 12)
      - Mission to Planet Earth, 1995-96
        - Amendment language (Box 89, Folder 13)
        - American Geophysical Union (AGU) (Box 89, Folder 14)
        - Appropriations correspondence - Harman/Bartlett (Box 89, Folder 15)
        - Background/press (Box 89, Folder 16)
        - Bartlett (Box 89, Folder 17)
        - Budget request (Box 89, Folder 18)
        - Commercial space bill (Box 89, Folder 19)
        - Committee bill, 1995 (Box 89, Folder 20)
        - Correspondence, miscellaneous (Box 90, Folder 1)
        - Earth Observing System common bus (Box 90, Folder 2)
        - Earth Observing System Data and Information System (Box 90, Folder 3)
        - EDS (Box 90, Folder 4)
        - "El Niño" (Box 90, Folder 5)
        - Event (Box 90, Folder 6)
        - Fact book (Box 90, Folder 7)
        - Fire (Box 90, Folder 8)
        - Fire - Arizona (Box 90, Folder 9)
        - Gardiner/Environmental Protection Agency (Box 90, Folder 10)
        - General Accounting Office refute (Box 90, Folder 11)
        - Goldin/Walker interchange on science (Box 90, Folder 12)
        - Harman statements (Box 90, Folder 13)
        - Harman/Boehlert colloquy (Box 90, Folder 14)
        - Hughes (Box 90, Folder 15)
        - Institute of Electrical and Electronics Engineers (IEEE) (Box 90, Folder 16)
        - Insurance industry (Box 90, Folder 17)
        - Kennel, Dr. Charles F. (Box 90, Folder 18)
        - Landsat data applications (Box 90, Folder 19)
        - Marshall (Box 90, Folder 20)
        - Matossian (Box 90, Folder 21)
        - Mika, Aram (Box 90, Folder 22)
        - Montreal Protocol (Box 90, Folder 23)
        - National Academy of Sciences (NAS) (Box 90, Folder 24-25)
        - National Aeronautics and Space Administration (NASA) (Box 90, Folder 26-27)
        - Policy bill FY 96 (Box 91, Folder 1)
        - Press (Box 91, Folder 2)
        - Rescoping/improvements (Box 91, Folder 3)
        - Risk (Box 91, Folder 4)
        - Scripps (Box 91, Folder 5)
        - Senate authorization (Box 91, Folder 6)
        - Sensenbrenner (Box 91, Folder 7)
        - Sparks report (Box 91, Folder 8)
        - Stennis (John C. Stennis Space Center) (Box 91, Folder 9)
        - Talking points (Box 91, Folder 10)
        - Testimony and statements (Box 91, Folder 11)
        - TRW (Box 91, Folder 12)
        - Uncosted carryover balances (Box 91, Folder 13)
        - United States Global Change Research Program (USGCRP) (Box 91, Folder 14)
        - Walker (Box 91, Folder 15)
        - Watkins (Box 91, Folder 16)
        - Weyerhauser (Box 91, Folder 17)
        - Whipping materials (Box 91, Folder 18)
      - Space and technology, 1993-97
        - Ace Clearwater (Box 91, Folder 19)
        - Advanced Liquid Metal Reactor (ALMR) program (Box 91, Folder 20)
        - Advanced Technology Program (ATP) (Box 91, Folder 21)
        - Advanced X-Ray Astrophysics Facility (AXAF) (Box 91, Folder 22)
        - Aeronautics (Box 92, Folder 1)
        - AeroVironment, Inc. (Box 92, Folder 2)
        - Biomixer (Box 92, Folder 3)
        - California Manufacturing Technology Center (CMTC) (Box 92, Folder 4)
        - Cassini JPL (Box 92, Folder 5)
        - Challenger Learning Center (Box 92, Folder 6)
        - Clean Air Now (Box 92, Folder 7)
        - Clipper chip (Box 92, Folder 8)
        - Coalition budget - research and development (Box 92, Folder 9)
        - Commerce Dept. in 36th Congressional District (Box 92, Folder 10)
        - Commerce-State-Justice appropriations FY 97 (Box 92, Folder 11)
        - Cooperative Research and Development Agreements (CRADAs) (Box 92, Folder 12)
        - Dept. of Energy Authorization FY 96 (Box 92, Folder 13)
        - Direct TV (Box 92, Folder 14)
        - Discovery (Box 92, Folder 15)
        - El Camino College (Box 92, Folder 16)
        - Environmental research and development (Box 92, Folder 17)
        - "Environmental Science Under Siege: Fringe Science and the 104th Congress," Rep. George Brown, Jr. (Box 92, Folder 18)
          [open]
        - Excellon (Box 92, Folder 19)
        - Federal Aviation Administration (FAA) (Box 93, Folder 1-2)
        - Food and Drug Administration (Box 93, Folder 3)
        - Fuel cells (Box 93, Folder 4)
        - Fusion (Box 93, Folder 5)
        - Gas Turbine-Modular Helium Reactor (GT-MHR) (Box 93, Folder 6)
        - Geostationary Operational Environmental Satellites (GOES) (Box 93, Folder 7)
        - Gingrich (Box 93, Folder 8)
        - Global Learning and Observations to Benefit the Environment program (GLOBE)/NOAA (Box 93, Folder 9)
        - Goldin visit, 1994-96 (Box 93, Folder 10-11)
        - Green technology (Box 93, Folder 12-14)
        - HR 1756 - Commerce Department dismantling (Box 93, Folder 15)
        - Hughes - general (Box 93, Folder 16)
        - Hydrogen (Box 93, Folder 17)
        - Illusion Inc. (Box 93, Folder 18)
        - Jet Propulsion Laboratory (JPL) (Box 94, Folder 1)
        - Komsat (Box 94, Folder 2)
        - Kotkin story (Box 94, Folder 3)
        - Mars Surveyor/Pathfinder (Box 94, Folder 4)
        - McDonnell Douglas (Box 94, Folder 5)
        - Metrics (Box 94, Folder 6)
        - Mission Home (Box 94, Folder 7)
        - National Aeronautics and Space Administration (NASA) (Box 94, Folder 8-18)
        - National Science Foundation (NSF) (Box 95, Folder 1)
        - Nuclear energy/waste (Box 95, Folder 2)
        - Odyssey/TRW (Box 95, Folder 3)
        - Office of Science and Technology Policy (OSTP)/space (Box 95, Folder 4)
        - Omnibus Science Authorization FY 97 (Box 95, Folder 5)
        - Research and development tax credit (Box 95, Folder 6)
        - Reusable launch vehicles (Box 95, Folder 7)
        - Right Consortium (Box 95, Folder 8)
        - Rockwell (Box 95, Folder 9)
        - Sea Grant (Box 95, Folder 10)
        - Sea Launch (Box 95, Folder 11)
        - Small Satellite Technology Initiative (SSTI) (Box 95, Folder 12)
        - South Bay Workshop of Governments (Box 95, Folder 13)
        - Space commercialization (Box 95, Folder 14)
        - Space Infrared Telescope Facility (SIRTF)/Stratospheric Observatory for Infrared Astronomy (SOFIA) (Box 95, Folder 15)
        - Space launch (Box 95, Folder 16)
        - Space nuclear power (Box 95, Folder 17)
        - Space science - general (Box 95, Folder 18)
        - Space shuttle (Box 95, Folder 19)
        - Space station (Box 95, Folder 20)
        - Space suits (Box 96, Folder 1)
        - Spectrum Astro (Box 96, Folder 2)
        - Thermal Electronics, Inc. (Box 96, Folder 3)
        - Tracking and Data Relay Satellites (TDRS) (Box 96, Folder 4)
        - University of California (Box 96, Folder 5)
        - Veterans Administration-Housing and Urban Development appropriations, FY 95-97 (Box 96, Folder 6-8)
        - Wildfires (Box 96, Folder 9)
        - Wyle Laboratories (Box 96, Folder 10)
      - Miscellaneous, 1994-97
        - City of Los Angeles (Box 96, Folder 11)
        - Electricity deregulation (Box 96, Folder 12)
        - Energy and Water appropriations, FY 95-97 (Box 96, Folder 13-15)
        - Federal Emergency Management Agency (Box 96, Folder 16)
        - Gas Turbine-Modular Helium Reactor (GT-MHR) (Box 96, Folder 17)
        - Kubota (Box 97, Folder 1)
        - Legal reform (Box 97, Folder 2)
        - Line item veto (Box 97, Folder 3)
        - Loyola Marymount University (Box 97, Folder 4)
        - National Energy Policy Act of 1992 (NEPA) (Box 97, Folder 5)
        - Patents (Box 97, Folder 6)
        - Right-to-Know Law (Box 97, Folder 7)
        - Risk assessment (Box 97, Folder 8)
        - Robinson helicopters (Box 97, Folder 9)
        - Terrorism (Box 97, Folder 10)
    - Ron Stone and Maria Alongi
      - Health care, 1995-98 (Box 97)
        - AIDS Project LA (Box 98, Folder 1)
        - Alzheimer's Disease (Box 98, Folder 2)
        - American Nurses Association (Box 98, Folder 3)
        - Breast cancer stamp (Box 98, Folder 4)
        - Chiropractic (Box 98, Folder 5)
        - Contraceptive coverage (Box 98, Folder 6)
        - Expansion of Portability Act (Box 98, Folder 7)
        - Families First (Box 98, Folder 8)
        - Food and Drug Administration reform (Box 98, Folder 9)
        - Genetic information non-discrimination (Box 98, Folder 10)
        - Hatch-Kennedy Act (Box 98, Folder 11)
        - Health Insurance Portability and Accountability Act (HIPAA) (Box 98, Folder 12)
        - Health Tech (Box 98, Folder 13)
        - HR 1415 - Patient Access to Responsible Care Act of 1997 (PARCA) (Box 98, Folder 14)
        - Little Company of Mary Health Services (Box 98, Folder 15)
        - Mammography quality standards (Box 98, Folder 16)
        - Managed care reform (Box 98, Folder 17)
        - Managed care reform vote (Box 99, Folder 1)
        - Medicaid (Box 99, Folder 2-4)
        - Medical savings account (Box 99, Folder 5)
        - Medicare (Box 99, Folder 6-7)
        - Medicare/Medicaid (Box 100, Folder 1-4)
        - Medicine cabinet (Box 100, Folder 5)
        - National Mammography Day (Box 100, Folder 6)
        - No Tobacco for Children Act (Box 100, Folder 7)
        - Osteoporosis (Box 100, Folder 8)
        - Tobacco settlement (Box 100, Folder 9)
        - Women, Infants and Children (WIC) nutrition program (Box 100, Folder 10)
        - Women's Health and Cancer Rights Act of 1997 (Box 100, Folder 11)
        - Women's Health Equity Act of 1996 (Box 100, Folder 12)
  - Project files, 1995-98
    - Aerospace Corporation (Box 101, Folder 1)
    - AIDS Healthcare Foundation (Box 101, Folder 2)
    - Alameda Corridor (Box 101, Folder 3)
    - EV Rental Cars/Jeffrey Pink (Box 101, Folder 4-5)
    - Federal Emergency Management Agency (Box 101, Folder 6-8)
    - Harman - Los Angeles Air Force Base renaming building (Box 101, Folder 9)
    - Hi-Shear technology (Box 101, Folder 10)
    - Lee, Reverend Kwang Duk, [see also SERIES VIII. PHOTOGRAPHS-Constituent services---Photographs with constituents] (Box 101, Folder 11)
    - Less-lethal weapons - Jaime Cuadros (Box 101, Folder 12)
    - Marina del Rey (Box 101, Folder 13)
    - Montrose-Del Amo DDT (Box 101, Folder 14)
    - Palos Verdes (Box 102, Folder 1-2)
    - Palos Verdes shelf - DDT/PCB contamination (Box 102, Folder 3)
    - Playa Vista (Box 102, Folder 4)
    - Polar Power (Box 102)
      - Part 1 (Box 102, Folder 5-6)
      - Part 2 (Box 103, Folder 1-2)
    - Port of Los Angeles (Box 103, Folder 3)
    - Port of Los Angeles - Pier 400 (Box 103, Folder 4)
    - Prisoners in Peru (Box 103, Folder 5)
    - Rochem (Box 103, Folder 6)
    - Toyota hybrid electric vehicle (Box 103, Folder 7)
    - Venice Family Clinic (Box 103, Folder 8)
    - Western Airlines employees' claim (Box 103, Folder 9)
  - Subject/issues files
    - Defense (Box 103)
      - B-2 bomber files (Box 103)
        - 1995 (Box 103, Folder 10-11)
        - FY 96 appropriations, [see also SERIES VIII. PHOTOGRAPHS-Legislative activities-Military-Miscellaneous] (Box 104, Folder 1-5)
        - 1996 (Box 104)
          - Part 1 (Box 104, Folder 6-7)
          - Part 2 (Box 105, Folder 1-4)
        - 1997 (Box 105, Folder 5-6)
        - 1998 (Box 105, Folder 7)
        - Deep Strike Weapons study, 1996-97 (Box 105, Folder 8)
        - Panel, 1998 (Box 105, Folder 9)
        - Studies and reports, [see also IX. AUDIOVISUAL MATERIALS-Computer media] (Box 106, Folder 1-4)
        - Work by congressional district (Box 106, Folder 5-7)
      - Big Think topics, 1997-98
        - Strategy/threats (Box 107, Folder 1-4)
        - Revolution in military affairs (Box 107)
          - Big Think forum, handouts (Box 107, Folder 5-6)
          - Restructuring defense - reports and briefings (Box 107)
            - Part 1 (Box 107, Folder 7-8)
            - Part 2 (Box 108, Folder 1-2)
        - Infrastructure reform (Box 108)
          - Part 1 (Box 108, Folder 3-7)
          - Part 2 (Box 109, Folder 1-4)
            [folder 4 open]
      - Budgets
        - FY 1996 (Box 109)
          - Part 1 (Box 110, Folder 1-9)
          - Part 2 (Box 111, Folder 1-6)
        - FY 1997
          - 36th District contractor issues (Box 111, Folder 7)
          - AIPAC Defense Appropriations Agenda (Box 111, Folder 8)
          - Appropriations bill (Box 112, Folder 1)
          - Budget book (Box 112, Folder 2-4)
          - Hammon computer files (Box 112, Folder 5-8)
          - HNSC, Dept. of Defense hearings (Box 112)
            - Part 1 (Box 112, Folder 9)
            - Part 2 (Box 113, Folder 1-4)
          - Requests (Box 113, Folder 5-6)
        - FY 1998
          - Budget request (Box 114, Folder 1)
          - Defense Authorization Conference (Box 114, Folder 2-5)
          - HNSC hearings and meetings (Box 114)
            - Research and Development Subcommittee organizational meeting, 11 Feb (Box 114, Folder 6)
            - Secretary of Defense/Chairman of the Joint Chiefs of Staff posture, 12 Feb (Box 114, Folder 7)
            - Future readiness, 27 Feb (Box 114, Folder 8)
            - Chem-Bio/domestic terrorism, 28 Feb (Box 114, Folder 9)
            - Commanders in chief (CINC) hearings, 4 Mar, 18 Mar (Box 114, Folder 10)
            - Service Chiefs, 4 Mar (Box 114, Folder 11)
            - Tactical air, 5 Mar (Box 115, Folder 1)
            - Ballistic Missile Defense (BMD), 6 Mar (Box 115, Folder 2)
            - Army modernization, 11 Mar (Box 115, Folder 3)
            - Service secretaries, 12 Mar (Box 115, Folder 4)
            - BMD/Russia Doctrine, 13 Mar (Box 115, Folder 5)
            - Unmanned aerial vehicles, 9 Apr (Box 115, Folder 6)
            - NATO, 17 Jul (Box 115, Folder 7)
            - Miscellaneous hearings (Box 115, Folder 8)
          - Mark-up book (Box 115, Folder 9-11)
          - Mark-up memos (Box 116, Folder 1)
          - Requests (Box 116, Folder 2-3)
          - Requests - late (Box 116, Folder 4-5)
          - Research and Development Subcommittee issues/overview (Box 116, Folder 6)
          - Supplemental and Omnibus reprogramming (Box 116, Folder 7)
        - FY 1999
          - Defense Authorization Conference (Box 117, Folder 1-3)
          - Dept. of Defense press releases (Box 117, Folder 4)
          - HNSC bill - HR 3616 (Box 117)
            - Part 1 (Box 117, Folder 5-6)
            - Part 2 (Box 118, Folder 1-5)
          - HNSC hearings (Box 118)
            - Response to domestic terrorism, 4 Nov 1997 (Box 118, Folder 6)
            - Quadrennial Defense Review/National Defense Panel, 29 Jan 1998 (Box 118, Folder 7)
            - Secretary of Defense/Chairman of the Joint Chiefs of Staff, 5 Feb (Box 118, Folder 8)
            - Threats, 12 Feb (Box 118, Folder 9)
            - Proliferation, 25 Feb (Box 118, Folder 10)
            - Modernization (Gansler), 26 Feb (Box 118, Folder 11)
            - Atlantic Command (ACOM)/Pacific Command (PACOM)/United States Forces Korea (USFK), 26 Feb (Box 119, Folder 1)
            - Navy/USMC modernization, 4 Mar (Box 119, Folder 2)
            - Army modernization, 4 Mar (Box 119, Folder 3)
            - U.S. European Command (EUCOM)/U.S. Central Command (CENTCOM), 5 Mar (Box 119, Folder 4)
            - Merchant Marine issues, 10 Mar (Box 119, Folder 5)
            - Air Force modernization, 10 Mar (Box 119, Folder 6)
            - Service chiefs, 12 Mar (Box 119, Folder 7)
            - Bosnia funding, 18 Mar (Box 119, Folder 8)
            - Russian security issues, 19 Mar (Box 119, Folder 9)
            - Readiness/personnel field hearing, 20 Mar (Box 119, Folder 10)
            - Service secretaries, 26 Mar (Box 119, Folder 11)
            - Long Range Airpower (Welch panel), 1 Apr (Box 120, Folder 1)
            - Air Force depots, 4 Jun (Box 120, Folder 2)
            - Information warfare, 11 Jun (Box 120, Folder 3)
            - Rumsfeld report, 16 Jul (Box 120, Folder 4)
            - Russia issues, 4 Aug (Box 120, Folder 5)
            - Iraq inspections, 15 Sep (Box 120, Folder 6)
            - Readiness, 23 Sep (Box 120, Folder 7)
            - Space power, 29 Sep (Box 120, Folder 8)
            - Readiness, 7 Oct (Box 120, Folder 9)
            - Modernization, 8 Oct (Box 120, Folder 10)
          - Mark-up prep book (Box 120, Folder 11)
          - Request letters from Harman (Box 120, Folder 12)
          - Senate Committee on Armed Services bill press release (Box 120, Folder 13)
      - Defense conversion/dual-use technology issues, 1993-98
        - California Manufacturing Technology Center (Box 120, Folder 14)
        - Conversion (Box 120, Folder 15-16)
        - Defense consolidation (Box 120, Folder 17)
        - Defense Reinvestment and High-Tech Job Creation Act (Box 121, Folder 1)